Can you think of a time something felt
clearly broken but you couldn't do
anything about it?
So I think a lot of the systems where so
we're college students, right? We're
undergrads. So I think the system we're
in, we struggle with it quite a bit but
there's not really anything we can do
about it. We go to a pretty big public
school um with 50,000 students. So it's
like you know four kids saying anything
isn't going to make any change and we
have like we every day we talk about
like random complaints that we have with
classes or administration the structure
in general whatever it might be funding
and uh usually it just remains a
conversation
and doesn't become action and I think
the reason is because there's no clear
path forward as to how it would result
in action or how there would be any
change.
Yes. basically struggling from the fact
that whether it's a democratic
institution or a small business that's
trying to make it work for their
employees, you don't find a way to
easily coalesce to uh I forgot what the
term is, but basically get enough people
to act at the right time to make a
change for something that you have a
vested interest in.
For sure.
Um have you found any people that have